(Sheldon:)Hold on. If you don't want to live
with Leonard, why don't you just tell him?
(Penny:)Well, you know how he is.
He's sensitive and emotional.
(Sheldon:)That's because he drinks
too much soy milk.
(Penny:)I don't know what else
we can do but tell them the truth.
(Sheldon:)I suppose there's no choice
but to face the crying...
(Sheldon:)...angry accusations,
and the high-pitched wails of despair.
(Penny:)Yeah. And who knows
how Amy will react.
(Howard:)Here's some more ice.
(Sheldon:)- Thanks.
- What were we thinking?
(Howard:)We should have just done it
the regular way.
(Bernadette:)Those Chinese acrobats in Cirque Du Soleil
made it look so easy.
(Howard:)Honestly, if I could bend that far,
what would I need with you?
(Bernadette:)If you could bend that far,
you'd be doing us both a favor.